Hollander, Louis Photographs 5643 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Louis Hollander Photographs
1913-1966
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Hollander, Louis
5643 P
4.5 cubic feet
4.5 linear ft.
Photographs.
This is a collection of photographs of Louis Hollander. Some of those photographs include events like the dedication of the Sidney Hillman Health Center and the 12th Annual Convention of the New York State CIO Held in Lake Placid, Sept. 6-8, 1951.
7561810
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, January 24, 2012
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, March 25, 2019
Scope and Contents
This is a collection of photographs of Louis Hollander. Some of those photographs include events like the dedication of the Sidney Hillman Health Center and the 12th Annual Convention of the New York State CIO Held in Lake Placid, Sept. 6-8, 1951.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5643: Louis Hollander Papers
Labor unions --Officials and employees.; Hollander, Louis, 1893-; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America -- Photographs
7561810
- 1936-1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  5 photographs
- 1936-1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  10 photographs
- 1936-1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- 1936-1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- 1936-1943 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1936-1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  11 photographs
- 1936-1943 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  2 photographs
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  2 photographs; 1 negative
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- 1944-1946 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  9 photographs
- 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  1 photograph
- 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  8 photographs
- 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- 1947-1948 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- 1949 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- 1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- 1949 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- 1949 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- 1949 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- 1949 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- 1949 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 1950 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  20 photographs
- 1950 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- 1950 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- 1950 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- 1950 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  21 photographs
- 1950 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  24 photographs
- 1951 - Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- 1951-Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- 1951-National CIO Convention: November 5, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- 1951-Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- 1951-Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- 1951-Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- 1951-Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- 1951 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- 1951-Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- 1951- Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- 1951-Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- 1951-Sidney Hillman Health Center Dedication: April 14, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  7 photographs
- 1951-N.Y. State C.I.O. 12th Annual Convention at Lake Placid, NY: Sept. 6-8, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- 1951-N.Y. State C.I.O. 12th Annual Convention at Lake Placid, NY: Sept. 6-8, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  22 photographs
- 1952-1953 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- 1954 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  23 photographs
- 1954 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  18 photographs
- 1954 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- 1954 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  15 photographs
- 1956 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- 1956 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- 1956 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  17 photographs
- 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  19 photographs
- 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  13 photographs
- 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- 1956-1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- 1960 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- 1957 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- 1958 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- 1958 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- 12th Biennial Convention of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Atlantic City, New Jersey, May 9-17, 1938 (Box 4OP, Folder 4)
- 17th Biennial Convention of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Cleveland, Ohio, May 15-19, 1950 (Box 4OP, Folder 3)
- 15th Biennial Convention of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Atlantic City, New Jersey, May 6-10, 1946 (Box 4OP, Folder 2)
- 16th Biennial Convention of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Atlantic City, New Jersey, May 10-14, 1948 (Box 4OP, Folder 1)
- 1961 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- 1962 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- 1962 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- 1962 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- 1962 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- 1963 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- 1963 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- 1964 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  16 photographs
- 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  4 photographs
- 1964-1966, 1946-1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- 1964-1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- 1964-1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Louis Hollander Garment Shop - 1913 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Judge Panken takes over new post in Children's Court; Jacob Potofsky, 1932-1940 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Union meetings and rallies (Box 6, Folder 5)
  12 photographs
- Photo of an unidentified man (Box 6, Folder 6)
  6 copies of the same photograph
- 1936 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Jacob Potofsky (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Amalgamated Rally; Jacob Potofsky: 1936 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  14 photographs
- 1921 - Political Activity (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 1935-1938 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Vincent La Capria (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Union Dinners and Meetings (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Political Activity; Jacob Potofsky (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Miscellaneous items found loose in the box, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  programs; invitations; envelopes; tickets
- Note (Box 7, Folder 1)
  21 photos, one poster?
- Photo on a block of wood (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Group photo (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Photo album all notations are in Hebrew? (Box 7, Folder 4)
  66 photographs
- The Book of the Amalgamated in New York 1914-1940 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  1 bound volume
- Photo album of children; New York Joint Board, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (Box 7, Folder 6)
  27 photographs
- Miscellaneous oversize items pulled from boxes 11 & 12, 1938-1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  2 newspaper clippings (Hebrew?) from 1938; The Traveler: Approved Guide to Shopping and Sightseeing; South Jamaica Houses; Fordham University, One Hundredth Anniversary Announcement; Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, Credential to the Thirteent
- Oversize photographs -, 1936-1957 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Luncheon tendered Sir Walter Citrine and Walter Schevenels (1936); Testimonial Luncheon to Hon. Louis Hollander (1937); Victory Banquet tendered to Councilman Louis Hollander(1937); Sears P.A.L. X-Mas Party, Loew's Kings Theatre (1938); New York Stat
- Oversize photographs - housed in box 4 OP - row 104 [over the map case], 1938-1950 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Twelfth Biennial convention, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (1938); 15th Biennial Convention, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (1946); 16th Biennial Convention, Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (1948)-[2 copies, back to back, in M
- Images digitized from the collection. (Box 10)